NWLB Region II Office Files and Cases 5311
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
For information concerning the cases, the user is referred to the following materials in the reference section of the school library. Bureau of National Affairs. War Labor Reports. Washington: The Bureau, 1942-1946. 28 vols. Bureau of National Affairs. Key to War labor Reports. Washington: The Bureau, 1946. The user may take the name of a company on the accompanying list and then locate this name in the "Cumulative Table of Cases" in the Key to War labor Reports. This table will indicate the volume and pages of War Labor Reports which contain data on the case in question. War Labor Reports contains the decision of the NWLB for this case in full text. Included for each case are the Board's directive order, the opinion of the Board and dissenting or separate concurring opinions when such exist, and the report and recommendations of the panel, arbitrator, hearing officer, as the case may be. The Key to War Labor Reports also indexes NWLB cases "oy subject or Issue and by industry. A list of cases has been placed at the beginning of Section I.
Correspondence files consist of the correspondence of the Second Regional War Labor Board for the year 1945 At the time of this writing this section is incomplete. The correspondence is filed alphabetically and that portion from "O" to "Z" is missing.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Steel industry and trade -- Employees -- United States.; Arbitration, Industrial -- United States.; Collective bargaining -- Steel industry -- United States.; United States. National War Labor Board (1942-1945)
5596244
- Checklist of Mimeographed Studies issued by Research and Statistics Branch; National War Labor Board, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Office of War Information National War Labor Board, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Wage Stabilization, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- NWLB Office of War Information, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- NWLB Wage Stabilization Board, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Office of War Information; National War Labor Board, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Eighteenth Monthly Report of the National War Labor Board, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Office of War Information National War Labor Board, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Mr. Vernon Jensen, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Mr. Vernon Jensen, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Manufacturers (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Ninth and Twelfth Monthly Report of the National War Labor Board, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Commission Method of Wage Payment, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Commission Method of Wage Payment Folder 2, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 111-12075-D A.G.W.I. Lines, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 111-12075-D A.G.W.I. Lines, 1945 (Box 1.2, Folder 1)
- 111-13953-D Air Reduction Sales, 1945 (Box 1.2, Folder 2)
- 111-1653-HO Air Reduction Sales Co., 1943 (Box 1.2, Folder 3)
- 111-14498-AR Alleghany Ludlum Steel Corp., 1945 (Box 1.2, Folder 4)
- 111-5668-D Allied Chemical & Dy (Barret Division), 1945 (Box 1.2, Folder 5)
- 111-12069-D Alpha Portland Cement Co., 1944-1945 (Box 1.2, Folder 6)
- 111-3223-HO Aluminum Co, of America (Messena Div.), 1945 (Box 1.2, Folder 7)
- 111-3223-HO Aluminum Co, of America, 1945 (Box 1.2, Folder 8)
- American Broke Shop Co. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 111-10001-D American Brake Shoes and Foundry Co., 1944 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 111-10540-D American Can Company, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 2nd Region. War Labor Board American Can Company and Federal Labor Union, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 2nd Region. War Labor Board American Can Company and Federal Labor Union, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 111-5957 American Can Co. (Newark Machine Service), 1944 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 111-10540a-D American Can Company, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- American Cooperage Company, Inc., 1945 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- American Cooperage Co., 1945 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- American Cyanamid Co. (Calco Chemical Div.), 1945 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 111 - 10574- D American Cystocope Makers Co., 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 111-16881-D American District Steam Company, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 111-8334-D American Hard Rubber Co., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- 4261-D American Locomotive 2-D-392, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 11-993-D American Locomotive Co., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- 111-2011-D American Platinum Company, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- 111-2637-D American Radiator & Standard sanitary Co., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 111-10095-Ho American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corp., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 111-10952-HO American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corp., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- 111-11385-HO American Radiator & Standard Sanitary Corp., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- 111-16-C American Rolbal Corp., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- 111-7077-D American Saw Mill Machinery Co., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- 111-11417-D American Smelting & Refining Co., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- 111-6617-D Amer. Smelting & Refill, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- 111-7679-D American Surety Co., 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 111-5032-D American Weighmaster Association, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 11-9927-HO Ames Iron Works, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Form #10 Application, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- 111-1328-HO Applied Optical Industries, Inc., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- 111-7051-D Arch Preserver Shoe Shop, Inc., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- 111-1372-D Archer-Daniels-Midland Company, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Armour & Company Arbitration, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- 111-6849-D Associated Fur & Training Manufacturers, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- 111-10870-D Associated Mirror Manufacturers., Inc., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- 111-1056-HO Atlantic Casting & Engineering Corp., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- 25-2990-A Atlantic Contracting Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- 111-9873-D Atlas Plywood Corp., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- 111-12372-D Auburn Spark Plug Co, Inc., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- 111-12653-D Automatic Paper Machinery Company, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- 111-9238-HO Aviation Packaging, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- National War Labor Board, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- 111-1443-D Babcock & Wilcox, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Supplemental Folder 111-1443-D Babcock & Wilcox Co., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- 111-14012-D Bakers & Co., Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Bakers & Co. Inc. Case No. III - 5501 - D Folder 1, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Bakers & Co. Inc. Case No. III - 5501 - D Folder 2, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Bakers & Co. Inc. Case No. III - 5501 - D Folder 3, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- 111-5887-HO Baker & Tayler Co., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- 111-5267-D Barrett & Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- 111-5267-D Barrett & Co., Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- 111-5140-D Bayonne Steel Products Co., 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- 111-2842-HO Beaunit Mills, Inc., 1943 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- 111-4450-D Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- 11-4522-D Bendix Aviation Corp., 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- 111-13040-D Bendix Aviation Corp., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- 111-9046-D Bendix Aviation Corp., 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- 111-8549-D Bennel Machine Co, Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- 111-10104-D Bergen Point Iron Works, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- 111-3644-D Bergen Point Iron Works, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- 111-2480-D Best Food, Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- 111-11702-HO Best Food, Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- 111-11293-D Bethlehem Steel Company, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- 111-4903-HO Bignall Foundry Co, Inc., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- 111-2374-D Bijur Lubricating Corp., 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- 111-6638-D Bliss (.E.W) Company, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- 111-2806-D Bliss & Laughlin Co., 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- 111-10894-HO Bloomingdale Bros, Inc., 1945 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- 111-297-C Blumenthal (B.) Co., 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- 111-7765-D Boehme (H.O.), 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- 111-1905-D Bommer Spring Hinger Co., 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- 111-12550-HO The Borden Company, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- 111-13015-D Bowen Products Corporation, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- 111-2802-D Breeze Corp, Inc. Folder 1, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- 111-2802-D Breeze Corp, Inc. Folder 2, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- 111-6350-D Brewers Bd. Of Trade, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- 111-3162-HO Brewers Board of Trade, Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- 111-1265-HO Brewers Bd. Of Trade Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- 111-1355-D Brick Mfg. Ass'n. of Inc., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- 111-1354-D Brite Specialty Company, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- 111-9387-HO Broad Street Club, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- 111-7111-HO Brooklyn Cooperage, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- 111-7111-MO Brooklyn Cooperage, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- 111-226-AR Brooklyn & Long Island Livery Assn., 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- 111-7183 Brooklyn Union Gas Co., 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Buffalo Bolt Company Wage Schedule Part 2, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Buffalo Bolt Company Wage Schedule Part 1, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Buffalo Bolt Company Schedule "B", 1944 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Buffalo Bolt Company Schedule "C", 1944 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Buffalo Bolt Company Schedule "A", 1944 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- 111-16352-D Buffalo Coal Dealers, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- 111-5031-D Buffalo Feed Mills Folder 1, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- 111-2802-D Breeze Corp, Inc. Folder 2, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- 111-2238-HO Buffalo Steel Fabrications, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- 111-13337-HO Buffalo Tank Corp., 1945 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- 111-10503-D Burkaw Electric Company, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- 111-13549-D Burns (Williams J) Detective Agency, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- 111-3388-D Bush Terminal Bldgs., 1945 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- 111-6762-D Caf Owners Guild, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- 111-8316-D Callite Tungsten Corp., 1945 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 111-603-D Canal Carrier's Assn., 1943-1945 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- 111-8541-D Carborundum Co., 1944 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- 111-4192-D Carborundum Co., 1945 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Cantrell & Cochrane Limited 111-17121-HO, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- 111-1514-HO Cantrell & Cochran Ltd., 1943 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- 111-10501-D The Carborundum Co., 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- 111-5313-D Carlton Lamp Co., 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- 111-6296-D Carol Cab Corporation, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- 111-8632-D Celanese Corp. of America, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- 111-7043-D Celanese Corporation Folder 1, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- 111-7043-D Celanese Corporation, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- 111-417-C Celotex Corp., 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- 111-863-D Central Foundry Co., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- 111-1463-D Century Curtain Co. Inc., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- 111-9149-D Century Projector Co., 1944 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- 111-9327-D Champion Aero Metal Products Inc., 1945 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- 111-6861-HO Chatillon (John), 1944 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- 111-12606-HO Circle Wire & Cable Corporation, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- 111-8943-D Clark Thread Company, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- 111-3386-D Cold Storage Warehouseman's Assn., 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- 111-938-D Colony Club, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- 111-7222-D Colombian Bronze, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- 2-42742 Colombian Products Corp., 1945 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- 111-11035-D Columbia Shade Mills, Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- 111-11035-D Columbia Shade Mills, Inc. Folder 2, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- 111-6226-HO Columbus McKinnon Chain-Corporation, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- 111-2911-D Comprehensive Omnibus Co.; East Side Omnibus Co., 1944 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- 111-4694-HO Decorated Metal MF Co, Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- 111-8803-D Detroit & Cleveland Navigation Company, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- 111-951-D Dewald Radio Mfg. Corp., 1943-1945 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- 111-9866-D Dexter Folder Co., 1945 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- 111-16028-HO Diamond Mills Paper Company, Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- 111-6636-D Diamond Expansion Bolt Co, Inc., 1944 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Diamond Silver Co., 1943 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Dictaphone Corp., 1945 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- 111-2948-HO Dietz (R.E.) Co, Inc., 1945 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- 111-8265-D D.N.X. Corporation, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- 111-6594-D Dover Boiler & Plates Fabricators, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- 111-2683-D Donner-Hanna Coke Co., 1943 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- 111-1662-D B.B. Crystal Company, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- 111-14334-D Cudahy Packing Company, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- 111-2752-D Cudahy Company, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- 111-15137-HO David Bell Company, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- 111-4763-HO Davidson (ML&T.) Co., 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- 111-8797-D Crucible Steel Com., 1944 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- 32352 Corning Glass Works, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- 111-2700-HO Cooper (Peter) Corp., 1943 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- 111-14217-HO COX & Stevens, Inc., 1945 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- 111-10146-D Continental Can Co., 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Consolidated Laundries Corp., 1943 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- 111-6739-D Continental Baking Co. (Winter Bread Division, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- 111-5454-D Dahlstrom Metallic Door Company, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- 111-1712-HO Davis Engineering Corp., 1944 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- 111-4935-D Davis (R.B.) Co., 1944 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- 111-7234-HO Dunkirk Radiator Corp., 1944 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- 111-12016-D Durham Dye Works, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- 111-11443-D E.A. Laboratories, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- 111-11443-D E.A. Laboratories, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- 111-2185-HO E.A. Laboratories, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- 111-5635-D Eagle Electric Mfg., 1943-1945 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- 111-5750-D Eagle Electric Mfg. Co., 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- 111-5249-D Eastern Air Device Inc., 1944 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- 111-7933-D Eastern Temperature Control Co., 1945 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- 111-3389-D Edison (Thomas A.) Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- 2-73490 Electrotypers & Stereotypers Assoc. of New York, Inc., 1943-1945 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- 111-7944-HO Elliot Galvanizing, 1943-1945 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- 111-1765-D Empire State Club, Inc., 1943-1945 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- 111-12557-D Endicott Johnson Corp., 1945 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- 111-9293-D Endicott Johnson Corp. (Three Tanneries), 1944-1945 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- IBWA-2511-Einhorn's, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- 111-7983-D Engleward (Charles) Inc., 1943-1945 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- 111-10332-JB Eppenbach, Inc., 1945 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- 111-13583-D Edward Ermold, Co., 1944-1945 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- 111-6453-D Ermold (Edward) Co., 1944-1945 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- 111-1127-D Essential Tool & Dye Corp., 1943 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- 111-423-AR Exchange Buffet Corp., 1943-1945 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- 111-6298-D Exchange Buffet Corp. Supplementary Folder, 1944-1945 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- 111-9421-D FADA Radio & Electric Company, 1944-1945 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- 111-10504-D Fairbanks Company, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- 111-1990-HO Fairchild Press Inc., 1943 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- 111-6329-D Falstrom Company, 1944-1945 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- 111-6329-D Falstrom Company Supp., 1944-1945 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- 111-9786-D Farber (S.W.) Inc., 1945 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- 111-14001-D Farrel Birmingham Co. Inc., 1945 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Federal Bearing s Company, Inc. Folder 1, 1944-1945 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Federal Bearing s Company, Inc. Folder 2, 1944-1945 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- 111-8262-D Feiner (P.) & Sons, Inc., 1945 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- 2-64361 Ferdinand Gumann & Co., 1945 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- 111-3102-HO Ferree (E.H.) Co., 1944-1945 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- 111-1357-D Fieldstone Tool & Machine Co., 1943-1945 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- 111-6143-D Fish Net & Twine Co., 1944 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- 2-39082 Flintkote Co., 1944-1945 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Foster Wheeler Corp., 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- 111-14328-D Foster Wheeler Corp., 1945 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- 111-10882-D Four Die Castings Cos, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Frankel Brothers & Company 11-46-C, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- 111-16386-D Fulton County Coal Dealers, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- 2-D-2 Fuld & Company, Inc., 1943 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- 111-7548-D Fuld and Company, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- 111-6254-D Fulton County Tanners Ass'n. Folder 1, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- 111-6254-D Fulton County Tanners Ass'n. Folder 2, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- 111-6354-D Fulton County Tanners Ass'n. (suppl. Folder), 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- 111-12235-D Fuld & Hatch Knitting Company, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- 111-3321-HO Fur Dressers Guild Inc., 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- 111-1164-D Gair (Robert) Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- 111-6457-D Garfield Mfg. Co., 1943-1945 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Gaylord Container Corp., 1943-1945 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- 111-7346-D Gem Electric Mfg. Co, Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- 111-12823-D Gemloid Corp., 1945 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- 111-6456-D General Baking Co., 1944 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- 111-5434-D General Cable Corp., 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- 111-11083-D General Cable Corporation, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- 2-73492 General Cable Corporation, 1943-1945 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- 111-11257-D General Cable Corp. Folder 1, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- 111-11257-D General Cable Corp. Folder 2, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- 111-7251-D General Cable Corp., 1944 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- 111-11257-D General Cable Corp., 1944 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- General Electric (Box 19, Folder 1)
- 111-4487-HO Gibbs & Cox, 1944 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- 111-3432-D Globe Forbes & Foundries, Inc., 1945 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- 111-1192-AR Globe Weine Corp., 1945 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- 111-15426-JB Goodrich (B.F.) Co., 1945 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- 111-11606-D Gotham Hotel Supply Co, Inc., 1945 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- 111-14625-HO Green Bus Lines, Inc., 1945 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- 111-3153-D Grey (C.M.) Mfg. Co., Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- 111-3153-D Grey (C.M.) Mfg. Co. Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- 111-9572-D Gulf Oil Corporation, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- 111-4253-HO Gulf Oil Corp. (New York Div.), 1944 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- 111-6344-D Hatfield Wire & Cable Company, 1944 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- 111-2033-D Helena Rubenstien, Inc., 1943-1945 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- 111-12552-D Helena Rubinstein, Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- 111-4699-D Heller Bros., Co., 1944 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- 111-462-AR Hendrick Hudson Hotel, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- 111-7506 Henry & Allen, Inc., 1944 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- 111-12912-HO Henry B. Cohen, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- 111-11737-D Highland and General Hospital, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- 111-328-AR Hoffman (s) & Co., 1943-1945 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- 111-682-D Hoffman Beverage Co., 1944-1945 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- 111-548-C Homelite Corp., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- 111-1006-D Hope's Windows, Inc., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- 2-D-36 Hope's Windows, Inc. Folder 1, 1943-1944 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- 2-D-36 Hope's Windows, Inc. Folder 2, 1943-1944 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- 111-6761-D Hotel Association of New York, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Houdville-Hershey Corp. (Houde Engineering), 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- 2-36926 Hudson Blue Print Co., 1943-1944 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- 111-7300-D Hudson Smelting Refinery Co, Inc., 1944 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- 111-7107-D Huguet Fabrics Corp., 1945 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- 111-3679-D Hygiene Company, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- 111-8720-D Hy-Score Arms Corps., 1945 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- 111-9706-HO Igoe Brothers, Inc., 1945 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- 111-13174-D Ingersoll-Rand Co., 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- 111-9542-D Interlock Metal Unites, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- 111-5579-HO Int'l. Cooperage Co., 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- 111-7688-Ho International Harvest Company, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- 111-11924-D International Harvester Co., 1945 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- 2-43066 International Plastic Corp., 1944-1945 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- 111-1743-HO Int'l. Smelting & Refining Co., 1943 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- 111-10072-D Iroquois China Company, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- 111-11770-D Irvington Varnish & Insulator Co., 1945 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- 111-13118-D Jacobs Brothers, Inc., 1945 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- WLB Kressler Mfg. Co., 1945 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- 111-7630-D Jamaica Buses, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- 111-12107-D Jamestown Worsted Mills, 1944-1945 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- 2-D-3 Jergens (Andrews) Co., 1943-1944 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- 111-5904-D Jerome Knitting Mills, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- 111-1341-D John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- 111-667-D Johns-Manville Corp., 1943-1944 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- 111-5161-D Julliard (A.D.) & Co. Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- 111-7159-D A.D. Juilliard Company, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- 111-9356-D Julius Kayser, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- 111-13735-D Kayser (Julius) and Company, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- 111-8801-D Haragheusian (A. &M) Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- 111-8705-HO Kelly Island Lime Transport Co., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- 2-75931 Kerby Saunders, Inc., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- 111-10274-D Widde (Walters & Co.) Inc., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- 111-10680-D Kingan & Company, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- 111-519-D Kings County Lighting, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- 111-8353-D Kings County Light Company, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- 111-12455-D Kirchberger (M.) Co, Inc., 1945 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- 2-62747 Korell Company, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- 2nd Region. War Labor Board L. O. Koven and Brothers, Inc. and Federal Labor Union Case No. 111-12712-D, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- 111-7639-D Koven (L.O.) & Bros., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- 111-6080-D Kraeuter & Co. Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- 111-1727-D Kramer & Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- 111-8910-HO Kriesler (Jacques) Mfg. Co., 1945 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- 111-1888-HO Lackawanna Steel Corp., 1945 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- 111-2398-D La Favorite Rubber Mfg., Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- 111-673-AR Lake Erie Engineering, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- 111-3057-HO Lakeside Bronze Inc., 1943 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- 111-2158-HO Lancaster Malleables & Steel Corp., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- 2-42295 Lapp Insulator Co. Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- 111-2105-D Larsen Baking Co., 1945 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- 111-3837-HO, 1944-1945 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- 111-12277-D Lederle Laboratories, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- 111-868-D Ledkote Products Co. Folder 1, 1943-1944 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- 111-868-D Ledkote Products Co. Folder 2, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- 111-868-D Ledmote Products, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Case No. 2-D-322, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- 111-1950-D Lever Brothers, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- 111-3762-D Leviton Mfg. Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- 2635-D Leviton Mfg., Co., 1944 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- 111-12942-HO Lignum Chemical Co, Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- 111-10928-D Linde Air Products Company, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- 111-12545-HO Lithographers & Printers Finishers Ass'n. Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- 111-2985-D Long Island Lighting Co. & Nassau & Suffolk, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- 111-8475-D Look, Inc., 1944 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- 111-969-HO Loose-Wiles Biscuit Company, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- 111-16418-HO Ludlow Valve Mfg. Co, Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- 111-15843-HO Ludlow Valve Mfg. Company, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- 111-5500-D Ludwig Baumann Company, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- 2-AR-16 McMillions (W.H.) Sons 11-203-AR, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- 2-71262 Mack Molding Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Marine Mfg. and Supply Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- 111-11294-D Maxson (W.L.) Corp., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- 111-3253-D Maxon (W.L.) Corp., 1944-1945 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- 111-3961-HO Matthews (S.H.) & Co. Folder 1, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- 111-3961-HO Matthews (S.H.) & Co., 1944 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- 111-800-D May Mfg. Corp., 1944 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- 111-10402-D R.H. Macy Co, Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- 111-10114-HO R.H. Macy & Co, Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- 111-1062-D Mack Manufacturing Corp. cross ref. 2-D-102, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 11)